file: install3.txt

FONT INSTALLATION INSTRUCTIONS

** Windows 95 and later versions **

• using an unzip utility, extract the font and manual to a location that you can find later (it doesn't matter where; putting it on the desktop is easiest, but it can go in any folder you like)
• activate the Start button on the taskbar
• choose Settings/Control Panel; a window will open
• if you can see the Cardo font file (icon with "TT" and the name Cardo), simply drag it onto the Fonts icon and it will be automatically installed

If you cannot see the Cardo font file, then
• double-click on the Fonts icon in Control Panel and a new window will open
• choose File/Install New Font (if you cannnot see the menu bar, tap the ALT key)
• in the dialog box that appears, navigate to the drive and directory where you extracted the font; Windows will search for font names
• double-click on Cardo
• close the Font window
• read or print the manual for additional information about using Cardo

*   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *

** Mac OS X **  (NB: this version of Cardo does not work on OS 8/9)

• using an unzip utility such as StuffIt, extract the font and manual to a location that you can find later (it doesn't matter where; putting it on the desktop is easiest, but it can go in any folder you like)
• double-click on the Cardo font file, which will open Font Book, OS X's built-in font manager; use Font Book's facilities to install Cardo
